Everyone.
I know everyone here worked hard
for today's performance.
Kotono.
Yes.
Sakura.
Rei.
Yes.
Nagisa.
Suzu.
Yes, indeed.
Saki.
Yes.
Chisa.
Y-Yes.
Shizuku.
Yeah.
Miss Haruko.
Yes.
Mei.
Yup!
To be honest, technique-wise,
we're far from perfect.
But all your efforts up until today
are engraved in you.
Give it everything you've got
now for this performance!
Yes!
Ready Kotono?
Yeah.
Hoshimi Productions!
--Let's...
--...go!
Fight!
Go, go, go! Yeah!
This stage is our very first step.
Are you watching...
...Mana?
"5 YEARS AGO"
"Hoshimi High School"
"Congratulations           "Welcome         "Spring
on your admission!"    New Students!"    Festival"
Hey, new students!
Promise me you'll make the next three years
an unforgettable high school experience!
--The light and shadow of youth.
--Next, each club will be coming up
to promote themselves!
--The light and shadow of youth.
--Next, each club will be coming up
to promote themselves!
--Of course, she's the light and I'm...
--Make sure to stay for it
if you're still undecided.
--Of course, she's the light and I'm...
--Makino, hurry up!
--But I'd recommend staying for it
even if you've decided, too!
--Makino, hurry up!
--But I'd recommend staying for it
even if you've decided, too!
--Coming!
They go all out for these presentations,
so please check them out!
After that, we'll move on to
the fun recreational activities!
Light and shadow don't mix inherently...
Why is she sitting next to me?
It's science next.
I'm so going to fall asleep!
After class?
Yup.
I want to talk to you about something.
It can't be now?
No!
Listen.
I better see you after school!
What was that about?
The emperor has abdicated
and by next autumn,
--As far as these things go...
--he shaved his head
and entered priesthood.
--It's usually a confession...
--He wandered the mountains
here and there
--No... There's no way that would happen to me.
--and devoted himself
to Buddhist training.
--The narrator speaks in a distinct tone
regarding the emperor.
--It must be one of those pranks or something.
--The narrator speaks in a distinct tone
regarding the emperor.
--They have great respect
towards the emperor.
--Do people still do those things?
--They have great respect
towards the emperor.
This will be on the test.
I guess so...
A prank?
What is?
What do you mean? Um...
This scenario...
I'm not sure what you're talking about.
Anyway, I have a favor to ask you, Makino.
An idol...?
Yeah...
Is that weird?
No.
I was just surprised because it was abrupt.
But well, I'd say you can become one.
Nagase, you can be an idol.
I think it would suit you, Nagase.
It's Mana!
What?
Just call me Mana.
Everyone else calls me that, too.
What... Um...
That's a bit...
It's totally fine!
All right...
Then...
Mana.
Good!
Then, Makino...
Oh, my first name is Kohei.
I knew that.
You can call me Kohei, too.
No, that would be weird.
I'm calling you Makino, okay?
If we call each other by our
first names out of the blue,
everyone would get suspicious.
That doesn't make any sense.
So...
It seems like the person who
scouted me is a famous producer.
Nagas--
That probably happens to you a lot, Mana.
That's not true.
It's never happened to me before,
so I don't know what to do.
But I am interested...
So I thought about it a lot
and consulted my little sister...
So, why me...?
W-Well.
Boys can be knowledgeable about idols, right?
It's not like all the guys are...
There's that complicated
Venus-something system, right?
I thought I'd consult someone
knowledgeable about that.
I'm not knowledgeable at all, either.
I would ask Furuta or Kawano about that--
I'm asking you, Makino!
I haven't told anyone else about this,
so don't tell anyone, okay?
I don't get it... Why me?
That's because...
You sit right next to me and it was convenient!
Purely proximity, huh?
So... About that favor I wanted to ask...
Yeah.
Actually...
"Hoshimi Productions"
Kohei Makino, a second-year in high school.
So you're classmates with Mana?
Yes.
What's your relationship?
Well...
We sit right next to each other.
Sit next to each other?
That's it?
Naga--
Mana and I've never really spoken at school...
That's not true!
We've spoken three times...
Or was it twice...?
Are you familiar with the Venus Program?
Yes, the general idea of it.
It's a ranking system for idols, right?
That's right.
Based on various data like popularity,
performance, and audience reaction,
an AI makes a judgment and
spits out the numeric data.
An AI...?
It's an attempt to have idols
compete under equal conditions.
It's sounding more like a sports game.
We'll be registering idols from our
agency in the Venus Program, too.
Mana, too, of course.
It's true that we're short-handed.
We'll have to hire someone eventually
to keep things running.
Since you're in school, you'll be
part-time until you graduate.
What? So that means...
You're hired.
Thank you very much, President.
That's too stuffy, just call me Saegusa.
To hire you part-time was one of the conditions
to get Mana to sign with us, anyway.
--Hey!
--What?
We had already decided to hire you.
Mr. Saegusa, you promised you wouldn't tell!
Oh, yeah?
Gosh!
Mana, I'm coming in.
Okay!
It's almost time for rehears--
What do you think?
It's... all right.
Look at me and say it.
I am looking.
How would you rate me out of 100?
Eighty-five...
Apparently, not being able to say 100
is the nature of Japanese people.
If I rated you 100 already,
what happens when you improve?
I, Mana Nagase,
will aim to be an idol that can't
be rated on a 100-point-scale!
Miss Nagase, it's time for rehearsal!
Coming!
"Newcomer Award"
"Idol Championship"
Pretty soon, I'll be a high school graduate.
Time flew by quick!
Oh, yeah!
Let's go for a drive soon!
Hey! Don't talk to me right now.
I just got my driver's license...
Here, say, "ah."
We're gonna be even busier after we graduate.
So you better brace yourself!
You better not forget you said that.
Graduate representative, Mana Nagase.
"Graduation"
Yes!
During my six years attending
Hoshimi Junior High and High School,
I've had various encounters.
Each encounter contributed to who I am today
and led to my current entertainment career.
I am grateful for the open-minded
teachers at this school...
Senpai!
Congratulations on graduating!
Are you staying for the concert?
"Mana Nagase Special Concert Stage"
Of course!
It's a privilege as a
Hoshimi High School student.
Happy graduation, Makino.
Congratulations, Mana.
Well, I better go!
Make sure you watch my last
concert as a high school student!
I will.
Wow!
After graduating high school,
I was promoted from a part-time
to a full-time employee at Hoshimi Productions.
"Hoshimi Productions"
"Reception Room"
The 14th Next Venus Grand Prix.
Will we be entering it this time?
I'll leave that decision to both of you.
Why didn't we enter it last year?
I deemed it was too early.
The Venus Grand Prix is
limited to newcomer idols only.
"14TH NEXT VENUS GRAND PRIX
Project Proposal"
If I win, I instantly join
the ranks of top idols.
Your current popularity doesn't apply.
Every participant starts off
from an equal baseline.
It will test your true abilities.
Um, I think I'll--
--I'll enter!
--What?
Let's do this!
You are my senior, Haruko!
It's our chance!
Only by two months...
Well, if you are entering...
I'll make sure I win, of course!
Haruko and I will both participate!
What?! What?!
M-Mana...
Let's do this together!
--All right!
--Oh, no...
I'm so nervous.
Do you have the confidence
to defeat all these rivals?
Who do you think I am?
Jeez.
You haven't changed at all, huh?
I can't afford to lose at this point.
I want to meet everyone's expectations.
For Haruko, who unfortunately lost...
For Mr. Saegusa and the staff...
And most importantly,
for my fans who support me.
You're right.
And plus a little for you, too, Makino.
I'm just an after-thought, huh?
This is as far as I go every time.
I can only watch you from here.
That's your job right, Makino?
Yeah.
Plus...
You being there...
...could be a source of power for me.
Here I go!
"Mana Nagase"
She did it!
Go, Mana!
"Mana Nagase"
"Hoshimi Productions"
It's the monumental final round.
I wanted you to take me there, Makino.
The traffic seems to be bad right now.
You better be there for my performance!
I'll head over as soon as I finish this errand.
All right, then.
I won't forgive you for being late,
even if you apologize.
Mana.
You made it to the final round.
You really are amazing.
Doing what I said I would is my policy.
Have I ever said any lies?
Lots of them.
Did I really?
You better be there no matter what, Makino.
If you're not there...
I'll be waiting for you.
Sorry for the wait.
It's true that she said a bunch of little lies.
But she never told a big lie.
Mana declared that she'd win.
Because she did, she really would.
That's how it felt.
Excuse me!
Are you from Hoshimi Productions?
Yes, I am.
Still nothing?
Come on.
They're taking too long.
It could be part of the performance.
"Hoshimi General Hospital"
"East Tower | West Tower"
"Emergency Room | Internal Medicine"
"Endoscopy Center | Cardiology"
"OPERATION IN SESSION"
Mana's accidental death became the biggest news
of the year when it reached the press.
And so...
The final round of the 14th
Next Venus Grand Prix
never commenced.
"2 YEARS AGO"
"Hoshimi Productions"
Makino?
Makino.
Oh, yes?
Is that your phone?
Yes, thank you for your call.
Yes, yes.
Being in the industry can make you
develop weird habits.
The day of the accident, I thought in the back
of my mind I was being involved in a prank.
The day of the final round...
She was sent off by herself...
The conditions were perfect.
Nothing's changed.
The instigator is Mana herself.
She'll come out laughing at
my dumbfounded face.
I would've been really mad.
But...
Even then...
That would've been...
...a lot more...
Makino.
No way.
Makino, over here.
Did I surprise you?
Mana...
Hey... So, it was a prank.
Suspicious as always, I see.
We've known each other so long,
let's have a little more trust.
Then stop doing things to startle me.
You're right.
Sorry!
That day, I met Mana again.
This time, as a ghost.
"TODAY"
Morning!
Well, don't you seem fired up?
Of course I am.
Interview day, was it?
What is it?
You look more like an interviewee
than an interviewer.
Well, excuse me.
But I'm three years older now,
unlike you.
Ghosts don't age!
You can still grow mentally.
I've been growing, thank you very much.
I'm a ghost, so let me take my time.
I feel like you're becoming more
and more of a slacker.
You used to shine brightly back in the day.
You know that's a taboo thing
to say to a popular idol!
That was when you were alive, right?
Were you doing interviews today?
Yes.
There may be a great increase in junior idols.
I'm happy to hear that.
Thank you very much.
But it gets me thinking of
my future career, too.
I'm sorry that I've been so useless...
That's not what I meant.
That's right. It's all your fault, Makino.
You're failing to bring out Haruko's charms.
I agree...
Huh?
I'm sorry, I was talking to myself!
Dummy.
I wonder what kind of girls we'll see today.
I'm looking forward to it.
"Hoshimi Productions"
Are you okay?
Thanks...
"From This First Step"